Hey everyone, welcome to this new video. It's about swimwear because LeoHex released these kind of
sportive swimsuits a while ago coated
PU suits and I finally got all the colors available. So five different colors
I'm going to show them all of you. So enjoy this video. When it comes to swimwear
It's always important to have a hair free bikini sewn, but for me, it's really time-consuming and annoying to
shave all the time so I tried something new. This is the ULiQ Sapphire Air 10 IPL hair removal device.
The big plus for me is it comes with a special bikini mode called SHR which is ideal to remove
individual stubborn hair. So normally I have to shave every other week especially before photo
shoots or videos but with this one I get long lasting hair removal results up to 24 months.
IPL means intense pulse light and with this light you basically destroy the roots of the hair.
This device here has a special cooling technology so it does not feel hot. I don't feel any pain.
It is really easy to use. It's fast and I get my results far easier than shaving every second day.
I'm not kidding here. The light is really intense so you have to use the goggles, the protective ones that are included.
Now if you're interested to find out more about IPL hair removal check out the You Like Sapphire 10.
I will put everything in a description text.
Also I have a discount code CELINE150 so check it out.
Now that I got rid of all the body hair I'm going to change into the first swimsuit.
And I will choose...
Purple.
first color is purple and I really really like the shine of the material I hope you can see that
in this light here and I also like the cut with the racer back here I think it looks really
sportive and cool so this is a swimsuit I would definitely wear trying to find the purple
highlights in my hair because it will match with the bodysuit anyway I like this color
I really do. It's the first time I'm wearing this one and it does work well together with the blue hair and also in general.
Next up is the leg.
Alright.
By the way, I've already worn this one on holiday last year in Egypt.
I can show you some pictures I took with it in the pool.
This is the classy one and there are a few things you should consider when wearing these kind of swimsuits to
pool or the sea. I will tell you more about it with the next color, but first I
will turn around and I see the mirror that the tag was showing here.
So here we go.
all right the green one so as I've mentioned before you have to take care of this material
to give it a long life and to be happy with it for a long time for example if you're going to
swim in the sea with it or wear it in a swimming pool as I did after wearing it please wash it out
with normal water so you don't have any salt water or chlorinated water left in the fabric.
This may be a swimsuit but this material is more delicate. It's not your average swimsuit fabric
so you have to take care of it and I did not have any problems when I wore it to the pool
and just simply rinsed it with normal water. Let it dry on a hanger. Another color gray and another
point I apparently can't mention enough is the sizing. We have Asian sizing here
so please if you consider ordering this swimsuit or other LeoHex items check
the sizing charts. I'm wearing extra large for example here and it fits me
really good because it's Asian sizing and if you order something and realize
when you try it on for the first time oh I'm not going to fit in there then just
leave it be and don't squeeze yourself into it because it will not it will not
work and you will ruin the item so again please check the sizing and just buy the
size even if it is extra extra large whatever which you don't normally wear
but in this case it might be the right size and this is the last color it's a
blue I'd say a purplish blue and I think my favorite color was of course black
and also purple I guess let me know in the comments what color is your favorite
and thanks a lot to Ulike for sponsoring this video what else to say then
have a nice day and I will see you in the next video bye